When it comes to family and relationships, there are no small surprises.
Gigantic is a comedy, romance film directed by Matt Aselton.
Young mattress salesman Brian decides to adopt a baby from China but is distracted when he forms
a relationship with quirky, wealthy Harriet whom he meets at his mattress store.
As their relationship flourishes, unbeknownst to
them, a hitman is trying to kill Brian.
Happy, played by Zooey Deschanel.
Happy's Father, played by John Goodman.
Brian, played by Paul Dano.
Kirby Weathersby, played by Ed Asner.
Barbara Weathersby, played by Jane Alexander.
John Weathersby, played by Ian Roberts.
Gigantic is a 2008 independent comedy film directed by Matt Aselton and starring Paul
Dano, Zooey Deschanel, John Goodman, Edward Asner and Jane Alexander.
The script, written by Aselton and his college friend Adam Nagata, tells of Brian (Dano), a mattress salesman who wishes to adopt a baby
from China, but finds himself sharing his passion with the quirky, wealthy Harriet (Deschanel) when they meet in his store.
The story was based on Aselton's childhood wish for
his parents to adopt a Chinese baby.
The film was shot in New York and Connecticut.
It had its world premiere at 2008's Toronto International Film Festival
and was released in the United States on April 3, 2009.
The film explores themes of department store,
adoption, chinese woman, stalker, stalking.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.